[
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0025",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 1,
    "question": "What would you do to travel to Jamaica?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Ice Fishing",
    "Wronganswer2": "Go Skating",
    "Wronganswer3": "Go Skiing",
    "CORRECT": "Bath In The Sea",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0044",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 2,
    "question": "What US city is \"NOLA\" referred to?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Oklahoma City",
    "Wronganswer2": "Tallahassee",
    "Wronganswer3": "Des Moines",
    "CORRECT": "New Orleans",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0017",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 3,
    "question": "Which set of three waterfalls is at the borders of the United States and Canada?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Iguazu Falls",
    "Wronganswer2": "Angel Falls",
    "Wronganswer3": "Gull Falls",
    "CORRECT": "Niagara Falls",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0073",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 4,
    "question": "Which country would you go to visit Alhambra Palace?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Switzerland",
    "Wronganswer2": "Croatia",
    "Wronganswer3": "England",
    "CORRECT": "Spain",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0063",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 5,
    "question": "There is a lake surroundrd by mountains in Nevada, which is it?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Victoria Nyanza",
    "Wronganswer2": "Lake Erie",
    "Wronganswer3": "Lake Superior",
    "CORRECT": "Lake Tahoe",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0065",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 6,
    "question": "To which city don't you need a passport to travel from New York?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Quebec",
    "Wronganswer2": "Madrid",
    "Wronganswer3": "Hainan",
    "CORRECT": "Dallas",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0031",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 7,
    "question": "Which class of a flight would enjoy the most premium service?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Executive Class",
    "Wronganswer2": "Economy Class",
    "Wronganswer3": "Cabin",
    "CORRECT": "First Class",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0009",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 8,
    "question": "One can visit the largest religious monument, Angkor Wat, in which country?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Ireland",
    "Wronganswer2": "Cuba",
    "Wronganswer3": "China",
    "CORRECT": "Cambodia",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0072",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 9,
    "question": "Disney World is located in which state?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Arkansas",
    "Wronganswer2": "Illinois",
    "Wronganswer3": "North Dakota",
    "CORRECT": "Florida",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0068",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 10,
    "question": "Which is NOT a ride-share app?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Uber",
    "Wronganswer2": "Lyft",
    "Wronganswer3": "RideScout",
    "CORRECT": "Google Maps",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0037",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 11,
    "question": "What are useful when go hiking in the woods?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Sunshades",
    "Wronganswer2": "Surfboards",
    "Wronganswer3": "High-heeled Shoes",
    "CORRECT": "Hiking Poles",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0066",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 12,
    "question": "Which is the largest wine growing and producing region in the United States?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Chateau Cheval Blanc",
    "Wronganswer2": "Scharffenberger Cellars",
    "Wronganswer3": "Handley",
    "CORRECT": "Napa",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0015",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 13,
    "question": "Which country is also called \"The Great White North\"?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Iceland",
    "Wronganswer2": "Greenland",
    "Wronganswer3": "Finland",
    "CORRECT": "Canada",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0014",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 14,
    "question": "In which country is Christ the Redeemer found as a monument?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Denmark",
    "Wronganswer2": "Honduras",
    "Wronganswer3": "Peru",
    "CORRECT": "Brazil",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0018",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 15,
    "question": "In which country is La Sagrada Familia a famous attraction?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Indonesia",
    "Wronganswer2": "Finland",
    "Wronganswer3": "France",
    "CORRECT": "Spain",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0001",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 16,
    "question": "Which city is also called \"The Big Apple\" in America?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Dallas",
    "Wronganswer2": "Ottawa",
    "Wronganswer3": "Chicago",
    "CORRECT": "New York",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0012",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 17,
    "question": "In which city is the Colosseum located?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Cario",
    "Wronganswer2": "Tokyo",
    "Wronganswer3": "Berlin",
    "CORRECT": "Rome",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0011",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 18,
    "question": "Which state does the National Park Yosemite locate?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Georgia",
    "Wronganswer2": "Maryland",
    "Wronganswer3": "Missouri",
    "CORRECT": "California",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0061",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 19,
    "question": "Which is NOT a real major airline of the US?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Alaska",
    "Wronganswer2": "JetBlue",
    "Wronganswer3": "Virgin Atlantic",
    "CORRECT": "Skymark",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0030",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 20,
    "question": "What paperless ticket enables travelers to fly with only a photo ID?",
    "Wronganswer1": "VIP Ticket",
    "Wronganswer2": "AA-Ticket",
    "Wronganswer3": "Visual Ticket",
    "CORRECT": "E-Ticket",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0039",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 21,
    "question": "You could enjoy beaches, see Komodo dragons and explore jungles, where are you?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Japan",
    "Wronganswer2": "Mexico",
    "Wronganswer3": "Greenland",
    "CORRECT": "Indonesia",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0060",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 22,
    "question": "Which season do you prefer to go skiing?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Summer",
    "Wronganswer2": "Spring",
    "Wronganswer3": "Autumn",
    "CORRECT": "Winter",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0038",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 23,
    "question": "You can reserve rooms at which website?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Paypal.com",
    "Wronganswer2": "Ebay.com",
    "Wronganswer3": "Linkedin.com",
    "CORRECT": "Hotels.com",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0035",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 24,
    "question": "What is a good place for surfing and sunbathing?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Stockholm",
    "Wronganswer2": "Greenland",
    "Wronganswer3": "Oslo",
    "CORRECT": "Hawaii",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0046",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 25,
    "question": "A flight traveling directly to its destination without connections or layovers is called a ...?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Unstoppable",
    "Wronganswer2": "Domestic",
    "Wronganswer3": "Helicopter",
    "CORRECT": "Nonstop",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0004",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 26,
    "question": "The \"Great Pyramids\" ,one of the wonders of the world, is in which country?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Russia",
    "Wronganswer2": "Vietnam",
    "Wronganswer3": "China",
    "CORRECT": "Egypt",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0042",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 27,
    "question": "You can reserve airlines at which website?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Flicker.com",
    "Wronganswer2": "Aol.com",
    "Wronganswer3": "Amazon",
    "CORRECT": "Kayak.com",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0054",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 28,
    "question": "Which country would you go skiing?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Malaysia",
    "Wronganswer2": "Mali",
    "Wronganswer3": "Sudan",
    "CORRECT": "Switzerland",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0074",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 29,
    "question": "In which country you would see the opera house like white sails about to take the wind?",
    "Wronganswer1": "France",
    "Wronganswer2": "Italy",
    "Wronganswer3": "USA",
    "CORRECT": "Australia",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0033",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 30,
    "question": "Where would you enjoy the Ouzo and Feta?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Canada",
    "Wronganswer2": "England",
    "Wronganswer3": "Turkey",
    "CORRECT": "Greece",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0027",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 31,
    "question": "What is used to authorize a passenger to get on a airplane?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Business License",
    "Wronganswer2": "All-Pass Card",
    "Wronganswer3": "VIP Ticket",
    "CORRECT": "Boarding Pass",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0071",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 32,
    "question": "Where would you find Madison Square Garden and Baseball Hall of Fame?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Wyoming",
    "Wronganswer2": "Iowa",
    "Wronganswer3": "Arizona",
    "CORRECT": "New York",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0032",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 33,
    "question": "The Tyne Bridge connects Gateshead to which city?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Manchester",
    "Wronganswer2": "Sunderland",
    "Wronganswer3": "Durham",
    "CORRECT": "Newcastle",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0020",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 34,
    "question": "Which French city is also called \"The City of Lights\"?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Lille",
    "Wronganswer2": "Montpellier",
    "Wronganswer3": "Strasbourg",
    "CORRECT": "Paris",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0036",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 35,
    "question": "You had better going to what state to see volcanoes?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Alaska",
    "Wronganswer2": "Texas",
    "Wronganswer3": "Washington",
    "CORRECT": "Hawaii",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0047",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 36,
    "question": "Which is a better place to go ice fishing?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Alabama",
    "Wronganswer2": "Utah",
    "Wronganswer3": "New Mexico",
    "CORRECT": "North Dakota",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0067",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 37,
    "question": "Which city are you in when you land in O'Hare?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Harrisburg",
    "Wronganswer2": "Santa Fe",
    "Wronganswer3": "Denver",
    "CORRECT": "Chicago",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0013",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 38,
    "question": "Which country is called \"The Emerald Isle\"?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Finland",
    "Wronganswer2": "Denmark",
    "Wronganswer3": "Canada",
    "CORRECT": "Ireland",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0059",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 39,
    "question": "Which country are you in when you land in Dulles International Airport?",
    "Wronganswer1": "France",
    "Wronganswer2": "Spain",
    "Wronganswer3": "Germany",
    "CORRECT": "USA",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0055",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 40,
    "question": "You could turn to whom to make a travel plan for you?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Insurance Agent",
    "Wronganswer2": "Yoga Teacher",
    "Wronganswer3": "Fund Manager",
    "CORRECT": "Travel Agent",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0062",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 41,
    "question": "If you were travelling by train, which company would you choose?",
    "Wronganswer1": "JetBlue",
    "Wronganswer2": "Delta",
    "Wronganswer3": "Virgin Atlantic",
    "CORRECT": "Amtrak",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0053",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 42,
    "question": "St. Moritz is a tiny mountain town known for skiing in which country?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Russia",
    "Wronganswer2": "Greece",
    "Wronganswer3": "Italy",
    "CORRECT": "Swiss",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0028",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 43,
    "question": "What US state is UCLA located in?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Texas",
    "Wronganswer2": "Arkansas",
    "Wronganswer3": "Illinois",
    "CORRECT": "California",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0021",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 44,
    "question": "How many passenger seats are on the Airbus A320 airplane?",
    "Wronganswer1": "50",
    "Wronganswer2": "450",
    "Wronganswer3": "3000",
    "CORRECT": "150",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0016",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 45,
    "question": "Which city of Ireland is known as \"The Fair City\"?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Waterford",
    "Wronganswer2": "Limerick",
    "Wronganswer3": "Galway",
    "CORRECT": "Dublin",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0050",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 46,
    "question": "Which country has the volcano Okinawa?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Turkey",
    "Wronganswer2": "Ukraine",
    "Wronganswer3": "Korea",
    "CORRECT": "Japan",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0006",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 47,
    "question": "In which country was the Incan citadel, Machu Picchu found?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Greece",
    "Wronganswer2": "Mexico",
    "Wronganswer3": "Canada",
    "CORRECT": "Peru",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0003",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 48,
    "question": "Which country is Eiffel Tower sitted in?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Russia",
    "Wronganswer2": "Iceland",
    "Wronganswer3": "Germany",
    "CORRECT": "France",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0075",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 49,
    "question": "In which UK county would you find Leeds Castle?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Cumbria",
    "Wronganswer2": "Suffolk",
    "Wronganswer3": "West Yorkshire",
    "CORRECT": "Kent",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0010",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 50,
    "question": "Which country is called the \"Land of the Rising Sun\"?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Brazil",
    "Wronganswer2": "Australia",
    "Wronganswer3": "America",
    "CORRECT": "Japan",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0040",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 51,
    "question": "If you want to see cherry blossoms, which country may be your destination?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Jamaica",
    "Wronganswer2": "Cuba",
    "Wronganswer3": "Iceland",
    "CORRECT": "Japan",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0024",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 52,
    "question": "In the south of the Caribbean is which island located ?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Maui",
    "Wronganswer2": "Fire Island",
    "Wronganswer3": "Christmas Island",
    "CORRECT": "Barbados",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0002",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 53,
    "question": "Of which of these countries can one find The Great Barrier Reef off the coast?",
    "Wronganswer1": "England",
    "Wronganswer2": "Greenland",
    "Wronganswer3": "South Africa",
    "CORRECT": "Australia",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0005",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 54,
    "question": "In which of these countries is Mount Fuji located?",
    "Wronganswer1": "China",
    "Wronganswer2": "Australia",
    "Wronganswer3": "Russia",
    "CORRECT": "Japan",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0029",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 55,
    "question": "How do you call the luggage you take on a plane?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Trapper Keepers",
    "Wronganswer2": "Backpacks",
    "Wronganswer3": "Hand Bags",
    "CORRECT": "Carry-On",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0049",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 56,
    "question": "What is the name of the a flight in which the travel takes place between the hours of 9pm and 7am?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Dark Flight",
    "Wronganswer2": "Sleepover",
    "Wronganswer3": "Pink-eye",
    "CORRECT": "Red-eye",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0058",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 57,
    "question": "Where would you travel for Shepherd's pie?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Brazil",
    "Wronganswer2": "Belgium",
    "Wronganswer3": "China",
    "CORRECT": "United Kingdom",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0043",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 58,
    "question": "What is the supplementary car rental insurance that covers accident damage called?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Life Insurance",
    "Wronganswer2": "Hubcap Insurance",
    "Wronganswer3": "Oopsie Fund",
    "CORRECT": "Loss Damage Waiver",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0034",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 59,
    "question": "You can travel the USA on which bus line?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Delta",
    "Wronganswer2": "Amtrak",
    "Wronganswer3": "UPS",
    "CORRECT": "Greyhound",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0051",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 60,
    "question": "Where would you go to enjoy K-Pop music?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Copenhagen, Denmark",
    "Wronganswer2": "Lisbon, Portugal",
    "Wronganswer3": "Ibiza, Spain",
    "CORRECT": "Seoul, Korea:",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0022",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 61,
    "question": "Which is the closest estimation of the distance between New York and Los Angeles?",
    "Wronganswer1": "150 Miles",
    "Wronganswer2": "18000 Miles",
    "Wronganswer3": "9000 Miles",
    "CORRECT": "3000 Miles",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0064",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 62,
    "question": "You would \"get your kicks\" on which long, east-west US Interstate ?",
    "Wronganswer1": "I-95",
    "Wronganswer2": "I-5",
    "Wronganswer3": "Highway 101",
    "CORRECT": "Route 66",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0041",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 63,
    "question": "Which of these is actually an airline of U.S.?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Jet Purple",
    "Wronganswer2": "Jet Pink",
    "Wronganswer3": "Jet Black",
    "CORRECT": "Jet Blue",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0008",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 64,
    "question": "The Windy City is a well-known name of which of these US cities?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Phoenix",
    "Wronganswer2": "Las Vegas",
    "Wronganswer3": "Orlando",
    "CORRECT": "Chicago",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0019",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 65,
    "question": "In which of these cities could one find the Sistine Chapel?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Athens",
    "Wronganswer2": "Berlin",
    "Wronganswer3": "Vienna",
    "CORRECT": "Vatican City",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0057",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 66,
    "question": "If you were at London Heathrow Airport, you would be in what country?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Spain",
    "Wronganswer2": "India",
    "Wronganswer3": "Holland",
    "CORRECT": "United Kingdom",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0069",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 67,
    "question": "Where would you go to see a Golden Knights game, a Raiders game, and to visit an Eiffel Tower?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Paris",
    "Wronganswer2": "Hong Kong",
    "Wronganswer3": "New Orleans",
    "CORRECT": "Las Vegas",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0023",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 68,
    "question": "How to get a better price for an airline ticket?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Bring Lunch",
    "Wronganswer2": "Fly Alone",
    "Wronganswer3": "Pay Cash",
    "CORRECT": "Advance Purchase",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0056",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 69,
    "question": "What is the name of the organization in charge of security for air flights in the USA?",
    "Wronganswer1": "CCCP",
    "Wronganswer2": "USP",
    "Wronganswer3": "CIA",
    "CORRECT": "TSA",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0007",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 70,
    "question": "In which US state can the natural wonder, the Grand Canyon, be found?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Michigan",
    "Wronganswer2": "Washington",
    "Wronganswer3": "Alabama",
    "CORRECT": "Arizona",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0045",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 71,
    "question": "How do people call the traveler that doesn't appear for their flight or hotel reservation?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Defaulter",
    "Wronganswer2": "Goner",
    "Wronganswer3": "Drop Out",
    "CORRECT": "No Show",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0052",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 0,
    "Rank": 72,
    "question": "If you are visiting Alaska in the winter,what would you bring with?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Sandals",
    "Wronganswer2": "Bathing Suit",
    "Wronganswer3": "Tank Top",
    "CORRECT": "Snow Boots",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0104",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 1,
    "question": "Where would you find a rainforest?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Norway",
    "Wronganswer2": "New York",
    "Wronganswer3": "Canada",
    "CORRECT": "South America",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0093",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 2,
    "question": "The Copenhagen Airport is located in which country?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Cuba",
    "Wronganswer2": "Portugal",
    "Wronganswer3": "Germany",
    "CORRECT": "Denmark",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0070",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 3,
    "question": "What is notable about a red eye flight?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Complimentary alcohol",
    "Wronganswer2": "Budget airline/seats",
    "Wronganswer3": "Unlimited free coffee",
    "CORRECT": "Very late/overnight flight",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0078",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 4,
    "question": "Denmark shares a bounday with which country?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Turkey",
    "Wronganswer2": "South Africa",
    "Wronganswer3": "Mexico",
    "CORRECT": "Germany",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0096",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 5,
    "question": "What is the party in Mexico called?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Carnival",
    "Wronganswer2": "Relaxa",
    "Wronganswer3": "Mardi Gras",
    "CORRECT": "Fiesta",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0094",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 6,
    "question": "Spain celebrates \"Todos los Santos\" on November 1st. What is its correspondent name in English?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Easter",
    "Wronganswer2": "Father's Day",
    "Wronganswer3": "Christmas",
    "CORRECT": "All Saints Day",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0081",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 7,
    "question": "What is the 3.2 million-year-old hominid skeleton discovered in 1974 in Ethiopiat called?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Prudence",
    "Wronganswer2": "Martha",
    "Wronganswer3": "Sadie",
    "CORRECT": "Lucy",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0084",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 8,
    "question": "What Moroccan city has a name that literally means \"white house\" in Spanish?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Beni Mellal",
    "Wronganswer2": "Marrakech",
    "Wronganswer3": "Boulemane",
    "CORRECT": "Casablanca",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0091",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 9,
    "question": "Land of Fire and Ice is a name of what country?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Crete",
    "Wronganswer2": "Cuba",
    "Wronganswer3": "Australia",
    "CORRECT": "Iceland",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0077",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 10,
    "question": "Which is traditional garb worn by Scottish men?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Army Jacket",
    "Wronganswer2": "Purple Shoes",
    "Wronganswer3": "Ponchos",
    "CORRECT": "Kilt",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0080",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 11,
    "question": "Scotland is the country with the most people with hair is what color?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Blonde",
    "Wronganswer2": "Black",
    "Wronganswer3": "Brown",
    "CORRECT": "Red",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0115",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 12,
    "question": "In what U.S. state is Louisville International Airport located?",
    "Wronganswer1": "North Carolina",
    "Wronganswer2": "Florida",
    "Wronganswer3": "Indiana",
    "CORRECT": "Kentucky",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0102",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 13,
    "question": "Europe does not contain which of these cities?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Berlin",
    "Wronganswer2": "Helsinki",
    "Wronganswer3": "Warsaw",
    "CORRECT": "Sydney",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0083",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 14,
    "question": "The 1942 romantic drama film starring Humphrey Bogart and Ingrid Bergman is set in what Moroccan city?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Rabat",
    "Wronganswer2": "Fez",
    "Wronganswer3": "Tangiers",
    "CORRECT": "Casablanca",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0117",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 15,
    "question": "The \"City of Brotherly Love\" is a famous name of which city?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Miami",
    "Wronganswer2": "Los Angeles",
    "Wronganswer3": "New York",
    "CORRECT": "Philadelphia",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0107",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 16,
    "question": "What country has cities such as Edinburgh, Glasgow and Dundee?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Peru",
    "Wronganswer2": "Mexico",
    "Wronganswer3": "Argentina",
    "CORRECT": "Scotland",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0103",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 17,
    "question": "Where is the deepest place in the world?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Bering Strait",
    "Wronganswer2": "Great Barrier Reef",
    "Wronganswer3": "South China Sea",
    "CORRECT": "Mariana Trench",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0100",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 18,
    "question": "What can be used to best describe the climate of Iceland?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Hot",
    "Wronganswer2": "Warm",
    "Wronganswer3": "Rainy",
    "CORRECT": "Cold",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0116",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 19,
    "question": "If you went to Jacksonville International Airport, you would be in what U.S. state?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Texas",
    "Wronganswer2": "Michigan",
    "Wronganswer3": "North Carolina",
    "CORRECT": "Florida",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0119",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 20,
    "question": "With culture of which island are Rastafarians and dreadlocks associated?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Ireland",
    "Wronganswer2": "Japan",
    "Wronganswer3": "Madagascar",
    "CORRECT": "Jamaica",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0111",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 21,
    "question": "What country shares a boundary with Alaska?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Japan",
    "Wronganswer2": "Ukraine",
    "Wronganswer3": "Finland",
    "CORRECT": "Canada",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0086",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 22,
    "question": "Along which two oceans does South Africa have a long coastline that stretches more than 2,500 km?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Pacific Ocean & Indian Ocean",
    "Wronganswer2": "Pacific Ocean & Atlantic Ocean",
    "Wronganswer3": "Atlantic Ocean & Arctic Ocean",
    "CORRECT": "Atlantic Ocean & Indian Ocean",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0090",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 23,
    "question": "The Continental Divide is part of which Colorado mountain?",
    "Wronganswer1": "The Front Range",
    "Wronganswer2": "The Sangre De Cristos",
    "Wronganswer3": "The San Juans",
    "CORRECT": "The Rockies",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0109",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 24,
    "question": "The Inca Empire is originated from what country?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Australia",
    "Wronganswer2": "Canada",
    "Wronganswer3": "France",
    "CORRECT": "Peru",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0092",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 25,
    "question": "With what culture are Floppy hats called \"berets\" associated?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Chinese",
    "Wronganswer2": "South African",
    "Wronganswer3": "Norwegian",
    "CORRECT": "French",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0048",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 26,
    "question": "Which is the tourist attraction visited most in the world?",
    "Wronganswer1": "The Great Wall",
    "Wronganswer2": "The Colosseum",
    "Wronganswer3": "Disneyworld",
    "CORRECT": "Times Square",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0087",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 27,
    "question": "Who is the auther of \"The Lord of the Rings\", an English born in Bloemfontein, South Africa?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Peter Jackson",
    "Wronganswer2": "C. S. Lewis",
    "Wronganswer3": "J. K. Rowling",
    "CORRECT": "J. R. R. Tolkien",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0026",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 28,
    "question": "What do Airlines referred the specific dates in which special fares or promotions do not apply as?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Global Dates",
    "Wronganswer2": "Holidates",
    "Wronganswer3": "Normal Days",
    "CORRECT": "Blackout Dates",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0114",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 29,
    "question": "Where do Poles, or Polish come from?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Indonesia",
    "Wronganswer2": "Mexico",
    "Wronganswer3": "Peru",
    "CORRECT": "Poland",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0076",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 30,
    "question": "The Space Shuttle usually take off from what state?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Nebraska",
    "Wronganswer2": "New York",
    "Wronganswer3": "Utah",
    "CORRECT": "Florida",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0097",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 31,
    "question": "Which country would celebrate Day of the Dead as a famous cultural custom?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Netherlands",
    "Wronganswer2": "Russia",
    "Wronganswer3": "New Zealand",
    "CORRECT": "Mexico",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0105",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 32,
    "question": "Which is a Pennsylvania city considered the \"Chocolate Capital\" of the U.S.?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Mars",
    "Wronganswer2": "Stover",
    "Wronganswer3": "Godiva",
    "CORRECT": "Hershey",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0106",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 33,
    "question": "What is the national forest in California which is the home of the world's largest tree called?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Mendocino",
    "Wronganswer2": "Sierra",
    "Wronganswer3": "Modoc",
    "CORRECT": "Sequoia",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0112",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 34,
    "question": "You might see kangaroos in the wild in which of these countries?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Sweden",
    "Wronganswer2": "Zimbabwe",
    "Wronganswer3": "China",
    "CORRECT": "Australia",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0108",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 35,
    "question": "It is what country that touches the Mediterranean Sea, the Bay of Biscay and the Atlantic Ocean?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Japan",
    "Wronganswer2": "Jamaica",
    "Wronganswer3": "Nigeria",
    "CORRECT": "Spain",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0113",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 36,
    "question": "Through which of these countries does the Nile River run?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Austria",
    "Wronganswer2": "New Zealand",
    "Wronganswer3": "Thailand",
    "CORRECT": "Egypt",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0082",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 37,
    "question": "What is the name of the animated movie that brought international recognition to \"hakuna matata\", a phrase commonly used in Kenya?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Toy Story",
    "Wronganswer2": "Beauty And The Beast",
    "Wronganswer3": "Monsters, Inc.",
    "CORRECT": "The Lion King",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0088",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 38,
    "question": "Which is the highest mountain in Africa located in northeastern Tanzania?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Mount Everest",
    "Wronganswer2": "Mount Elbrus",
    "Wronganswer3": "Mount Aconcagua",
    "CORRECT": "Mount Kilimanjaro",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0118",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 39,
    "question": "At Niagara Falls what phenomenon is frequently seen?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Butterfly Migration",
    "Wronganswer2": "Mud Slide",
    "Wronganswer3": "Dust Bowl",
    "CORRECT": "Rainbow",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0101",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 40,
    "question": "Music City is a name of which U.S. city?",
    "Wronganswer1": "New Orleans, LA",
    "Wronganswer2": "Hollywood, CA",
    "Wronganswer3": "Pittsburgh, PA",
    "CORRECT": "Nashville, TN",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0079",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 41,
    "question": "What is the name of the tallest mountain in Greece?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Mount Everest",
    "Wronganswer2": "Mount Fuji",
    "Wronganswer3": "Mount Smolikas",
    "CORRECT": "Mount Olympus",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0110",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 42,
    "question": "What mountain range would be found in Peru?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Appalachian Mountains",
    "Wronganswer2": "Rocky Mountains",
    "Wronganswer3": "Alps",
    "CORRECT": "Andes Mountains",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0085",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 43,
    "question": "On both the Atlantic Ocean and what sea does Morocco have coastlines as one of only three countries?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Red Sea",
    "Wronganswer2": "Caribbean Sea",
    "Wronganswer3": "Norwegian Sea",
    "CORRECT": "Mediterranean Sea",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0098",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 44,
    "question": "It is in which country that Mah Jong is the most common game?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Pakistan",
    "Wronganswer2": "UAE",
    "Wronganswer3": "Australia",
    "CORRECT": "China",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0095",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 45,
    "question": "Milwaukee, Wisconsin home refers to what famous motocycle company?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Suzuki",
    "Wronganswer2": "Honda",
    "Wronganswer3": "Isuzu",
    "CORRECT": "Harley-Davidson",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0120",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 46,
    "question": "In which direction from Cuba does the Gulf of Mexico lie?",
    "Wronganswer1": "North",
    "Wronganswer2": "East",
    "Wronganswer3": "South",
    "CORRECT": "West",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0099",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 1,
    "Rank": 47,
    "question": "It is in which country that Kimchi is a common food?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Belgium",
    "Wronganswer2": "Japan",
    "Wronganswer3": "Iraq",
    "CORRECT": "Korea",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0162",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 1,
    "question": "How many kilometers of coastline does Cuba approximately have?",
    "Wronganswer1": "15,000 Km",
    "Wronganswer2": "59,000 Km",
    "Wronganswer3": "200 Km",
    "CORRECT": "3,700 Km",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0140",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 2,
    "question": "It is a replica of what building in Athens, Greece, that stands in Nashville's Centennial Park?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Great Pyramid",
    "Wronganswer2": "Colosseum",
    "Wronganswer3": "Erechtheum",
    "CORRECT": "Parthenon",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0132",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 3,
    "question": "Kentucky bluegrass is in what color?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Blue",
    "Wronganswer2": "Purple",
    "Wronganswer3": "Red",
    "CORRECT": "Green",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0171",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 4,
    "question": "If you went to Martha's Vineyard Airport, you would be in what U.S. state?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Florida",
    "Wronganswer2": "New Hampshire",
    "Wronganswer3": "Alaska",
    "CORRECT": "Massachusetts",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0139",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 5,
    "question": "It is what beach area that is a popular South Carolina tourist attraction?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Virginia Beach",
    "Wronganswer2": "Hilton Head",
    "Wronganswer3": "St. Simons",
    "CORRECT": "Myrtle Beach",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0147",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 6,
    "question": "What country shares boundary with Germany, the Czech Republic, Slovakia and the Ukraine?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Chile",
    "Wronganswer2": "Haiti",
    "Wronganswer3": "India",
    "CORRECT": "Poland",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0175",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 7,
    "question": "Which is the tallest mountain in Africa?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Tanzania Peak",
    "Wronganswer2": "Mount Stella",
    "Wronganswer3": "Victoria Peak",
    "CORRECT": "Mount Kilimanjaro",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0172",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 8,
    "question": "In what place would you use \"buenos dias\" (good morning) and \"buenas noches\"(good evening)?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Japan",
    "Wronganswer2": "Chile",
    "Wronganswer3": "Mexico",
    "CORRECT": "Bolivia",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0121",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 9,
    "question": "It is which country that is split into 443 named islands and also holds the territory of Greenland?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Kenya",
    "Wronganswer2": "Canada",
    "Wronganswer3": "Japan",
    "CORRECT": "Denmark",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0156",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 10,
    "question": "The largest city in the Americas is what city in Brazil?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Lahore",
    "Wronganswer2": "Mexico City",
    "Wronganswer3": "Lagos",
    "CORRECT": "Sao Paulo",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0152",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 11,
    "question": "On the South Atlantic coast, what is the second largest city in Brazil is called?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Luanda",
    "Wronganswer2": "Foshan",
    "Wronganswer3": "Santiago",
    "CORRECT": "Rio de Janeiro",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0149",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 12,
    "question": "What do the active volcanoes in Iceland spew?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Slime",
    "Wronganswer2": "Ice",
    "Wronganswer3": "Concrete",
    "CORRECT": "Lava",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0148",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 13,
    "question": "It is what country that has the eighth-largest population in Europe with approximately 38.5 million residents?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Denmark",
    "Wronganswer2": "Scotland",
    "Wronganswer3": "Nicaragua",
    "CORRECT": "Poland",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0138",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 14,
    "question": "You would find the Abbey Road popularized by The Beatles in what U.K. city?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Liverpool",
    "Wronganswer2": "Glasgow",
    "Wronganswer3": "Manchester",
    "CORRECT": "London",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0127",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 15,
    "question": "In which part of the African continent is the Democratic Republic of the Congo located?",
    "Wronganswer1": "North",
    "Wronganswer2": "West",
    "Wronganswer3": "East",
    "CORRECT": "Central",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0128",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 16,
    "question": "Of which major lake does the southern part of Uganda include a substantial portion?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Lake Tanganyika",
    "Wronganswer2": "Lake Malawi",
    "Wronganswer3": "Lake Turkana",
    "CORRECT": "Lake Victoria",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0122",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 17,
    "question": "What island does the Queensboro Bridge cross over between Queens and Manhattan?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Fisher Island",
    "Wronganswer2": "Fire Island",
    "Wronganswer3": "Coney Island",
    "CORRECT": "Roosevelt Island",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0153",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 18,
    "question": "What instrument is a special in Mexican mariachi bands?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Cello",
    "Wronganswer2": "Piano",
    "Wronganswer3": "Tuba",
    "CORRECT": "Trumpet",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0150",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 19,
    "question": "You would find fried meatballs served with potatoes and gravy called frikadeller in which country?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Brazil",
    "Wronganswer2": "Jamaica",
    "Wronganswer3": "Mexico",
    "CORRECT": "Denmark",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0131",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 20,
    "question": "What sea does the eastern shores belong to where Latvia lies on ?",
    "Wronganswer1": "North Sea",
    "Wronganswer2": "Norwegian Sea",
    "Wronganswer3": "Mediterranean Sea",
    "CORRECT": "Baltic Sea",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0159",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 21,
    "question": "The \"Pearl of the Orient\" and \"Paris of the East\" are two famous names referring to which Chinese city?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Lima",
    "Wronganswer2": "Karachi",
    "Wronganswer3": "Ahmedabad",
    "CORRECT": "Shanghai",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0174",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 22,
    "question": "It is what highway that can one follow all the way up the coast of California?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Interstate 5",
    "Wronganswer2": "U.S. 287",
    "Wronganswer3": "Route 66",
    "CORRECT": "Highway 1",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0135",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 23,
    "question": "It is in which Asian country that Namaste with folding hands is a customary greeting?",
    "Wronganswer1": "China",
    "Wronganswer2": "Japan",
    "Wronganswer3": "Mongolia",
    "CORRECT": "India",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0176",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 24,
    "question": "Whose name is Spanish for \"mountain\" among the following states?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Wyoming",
    "Wronganswer2": "Oklahoma",
    "Wronganswer3": "Iowa",
    "CORRECT": "Montana",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0146",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 25,
    "question": "Where is the sacred River Ganges loacted?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Cuba",
    "Wronganswer2": "England",
    "Wronganswer3": "Venezuela",
    "CORRECT": "India",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0124",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 26,
    "question": "It is after what mountain that Mount Kenya is the second-highest in Africa?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Mount Everest",
    "Wronganswer2": "Mount Elbrus",
    "Wronganswer3": "Mount Aconcagua",
    "CORRECT": "Mount Kilimanjaro",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0130",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 27,
    "question": "Which sea of the Atlantic Ocean separates Estonia from Finland?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Aegean Sea",
    "Wronganswer2": "Mediterranean Sea",
    "Wronganswer3": "Black Sea",
    "CORRECT": "Baltic Sea",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0169",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 28,
    "question": "Hawaii is located in what mountain range?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Central Time",
    "Wronganswer2": "Pacific Time",
    "Wronganswer3": "Mountain Time",
    "CORRECT": "Hawaiian Standard Time",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0125",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 29,
    "question": "What is the Africa's largest lake called, which Kenya shares with Tanzania and Uganda?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Lake Chad",
    "Wronganswer2": "Lake Tanganyika",
    "Wronganswer3": "Lake Malawi",
    "CORRECT": "Lake Victoria",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0158",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 30,
    "question": "What is the city square in the center of Beijing, China that is the fourth largest city square in the world?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Rizal Park",
    "Wronganswer2": "Piazza Carlo III Of Bourbon",
    "Wronganswer3": "Kuybyshev Square",
    "CORRECT": "Tiananmen Square",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0168",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 31,
    "question": "What California city is the center of a metropolis that spans five counties?",
    "Wronganswer1": "San Bernardino",
    "Wronganswer2": "San Diego",
    "Wronganswer3": "San Francisco",
    "CORRECT": "Los Angeles",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0178",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 32,
    "question": "It is which Las Vegas hotel that was imploded in 1993?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Sands",
    "Wronganswer2": "Sahara",
    "Wronganswer3": "Bellagio",
    "CORRECT": "Dunes",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0142",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 33,
    "question": "Which country holds a largely Nordic and Gaelic population?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Brazil",
    "Wronganswer2": "South Africa",
    "Wronganswer3": "Cuba",
    "CORRECT": "Iceland",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0160",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 34,
    "question": "Walt Disney opened his first amusement park in which U.S. state?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Florida",
    "Wronganswer2": "New York",
    "Wronganswer3": "New Mexico",
    "CORRECT": "California",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0144",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 35,
    "question": "You would say \"Auf Wiedersehen\" to say \"good-bye\" in which country?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Costa Rica",
    "Wronganswer2": "India",
    "Wronganswer3": "China",
    "CORRECT": "Germany",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0173",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 36,
    "question": "Which commercial intersection in Manhattan, New York City is referred as \"The Crossroads of the World\"?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Times Center",
    "Wronganswer2": "Times Avenue",
    "Wronganswer3": "Times Street",
    "CORRECT": "Times Square",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0133",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 37,
    "question": "In what city is Alamo located?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Dallas",
    "Wronganswer2": "Austin",
    "Wronganswer3": "Houston",
    "CORRECT": "San Antonio",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0167",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 38,
    "question": "What is the name of the Las Vegas hotel which is shaped like a castle?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Bellagio",
    "Wronganswer2": "MGM Grand",
    "Wronganswer3": "Luxor",
    "CORRECT": "Excalibur",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0134",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 39,
    "question": "It is in what county that you are expected to say \"kampai!\" instead of \"Cheers\"?",
    "Wronganswer1": "India",
    "Wronganswer2": "Indonesia",
    "Wronganswer3": "Russia",
    "CORRECT": "Japan",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0123",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 40,
    "question": "It is what body of water that separates Scotland from Norway?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Pentland Firth",
    "Wronganswer2": "Gruinard Bay",
    "Wronganswer3": "North Channel",
    "CORRECT": "North Sea",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0163",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 41,
    "question": "First Lady of Waikiki is a famous name of which hotel?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Aston Honolulu",
    "Wronganswer2": "Halekulani",
    "Wronganswer3": "Hawaii Inn",
    "CORRECT": "Moana",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0155",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 42,
    "question": "Which major pharmaceutical company has its headquarter in the city of Berlin?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Novartis",
    "Wronganswer2": "Merck & Co",
    "Wronganswer3": "Eli Lilly & Co.",
    "CORRECT": "Bayer Health Care",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0179",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 43,
    "question": "It is in what country that Tandoor ovens are used for baking breads, such as naan?",
    "Wronganswer1": "France",
    "Wronganswer2": "Taiwan",
    "Wronganswer3": "Tahiti",
    "CORRECT": "India",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0129",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 44,
    "question": "Which is the largest fall in the world at the border between Zambia and Zimbabwe?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Chavuma Falls",
    "Wronganswer2": "Ngonye Falls",
    "Wronganswer3": "Sioma Falls",
    "CORRECT": "Victoria Falls",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0164",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 45,
    "question": "Which French actor playing the title role in \"Leon: The Professional\" was born in Casablanca, Morocco?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Gerard Depardieu",
    "Wronganswer2": "Vincent Cassel",
    "Wronganswer3": "Jean Dujardin",
    "CORRECT": "Jean Reno",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0165",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 46,
    "question": "What is the character in a series of suspense novels by Thomas Harris who was born in Lithuania?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Han Solo",
    "Wronganswer2": "Hans Gruber",
    "Wronganswer3": "Hansel",
    "CORRECT": "Hannibal Lecter",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0151",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 47,
    "question": "What is the name of one of the world's largest observation wheel, situated on the South Bank of the Thames in London?",
    "Wronganswer1": "London Nose",
    "Wronganswer2": "London Ear",
    "Wronganswer3": "London Mouth",
    "CORRECT": "London Eye",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0137",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 48,
    "question": "Which country is home of the world's highest mountain and has Katmandu as its capital?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Pakistan",
    "Wronganswer2": "Tibet",
    "Wronganswer3": "Peru",
    "CORRECT": "Nepal",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0166",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 49,
    "question": "You will mostly find what type of meat in the German fast food treat currywurst?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Lamb",
    "Wronganswer2": "Turkey",
    "Wronganswer3": "Chicken",
    "CORRECT": "Pork",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0170",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 50,
    "question": "What is the mountain range that forms the northern border of Italy called?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Rockies",
    "Wronganswer2": "Macaroni",
    "Wronganswer3": "Andes",
    "CORRECT": "Alps",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0177",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 51,
    "question": "What is the largest island in the Mediterranean Sea called?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Crete",
    "Wronganswer2": "Sardinia",
    "Wronganswer3": "Cyprus",
    "CORRECT": "Sicily",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0161",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 52,
    "question": "Between which two bodies of water is Cuba situated?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Atlantic And Pacific Oceans",
    "Wronganswer2": "Pacific And Indian Oceans",
    "Wronganswer3": "Carribean Sea And Panama Canal",
    "CORRECT": "Caribbean Sea And Atlantic Ocean",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0141",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 53,
    "question": "In what country does popular styles of dress include the sari for women and the dhoti for men?",
    "Wronganswer1": "England",
    "Wronganswer2": "Scotland",
    "Wronganswer3": "Australia",
    "CORRECT": "India",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0145",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 54,
    "question": "Stories of what mythical green creatures are often included in Irish folklore?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Bigfoot",
    "Wronganswer2": "Fairies",
    "Wronganswer3": "Tasmanian Devil",
    "CORRECT": "Leprechauns",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0143",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 55,
    "question": "It is which hall of fame that is located in Cleveland, Ohio?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Baseball",
    "Wronganswer2": "Basketball",
    "Wronganswer3": "Trumpet",
    "CORRECT": "Rock And Roll",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0157",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 56,
    "question": "Sampa is a famous colloquial name of what Brazilian city?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Mexico City",
    "Wronganswer2": "Lima",
    "Wronganswer3": "Bangalore",
    "CORRECT": "Sao Paulo",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0154",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 57,
    "question": "You may find which of the following endangered species in the Grand Canyon?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Black Rhino",
    "Wronganswer2": "Mountain Gorilla",
    "Wronganswer3": "Jaguar",
    "CORRECT": "Bald Eagle",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0136",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 58,
    "question": "What is the name of Russia's second largest city after Moscow?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Kinshasa",
    "Wronganswer2": "Jakarta",
    "Wronganswer3": "Istanbul",
    "CORRECT": "Saint Petersburg",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0126",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 2,
    "Rank": 59,
    "question": "It is what vast plain in Tanzania that hosts the largest terrestrial mammal migration in the world?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Ruaha",
    "Wronganswer2": "Mikumi",
    "Wronganswer3": "Tarangire",
    "CORRECT": "Serengeti",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0209",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 3,
    "Rank": 2,
    "question": "Which is the capital of Lithuania and also the second-largest city of the Baltic states?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Kaunas",
    "Wronganswer2": "Klaipeda",
    "Wronganswer3": "Siauliai",
    "CORRECT": "Vilnius",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0199",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 3,
    "Rank": 3,
    "question": "Which word is \"ty\" in Polish?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Love",
    "Wronganswer2": "Sorry",
    "Wronganswer3": "Bye",
    "CORRECT": "You",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0215",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 3,
    "Rank": 5,
    "question": "Person from what city in Mexico is usually called as Chilango?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Sao Paulo",
    "Wronganswer2": "Kinshasa",
    "Wronganswer3": "Bogota",
    "CORRECT": "Mexico City",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0184",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 3,
    "Rank": 6,
    "question": "Known as the \"Green City in the Sun\", what is the capital and largest city of Kenya?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Mombasa",
    "Wronganswer2": "Kisumu",
    "Wronganswer3": "Nakuru",
    "CORRECT": "Nairobi",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0192",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 3,
    "Rank": 22,
    "question": "Which city founded in 1907 only became Rwanda's capital when the country take independence in 1962?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Nyanza",
    "Wronganswer2": "Butare",
    "Wronganswer3": "Gitarama",
    "CORRECT": "Kigali",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0214",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 3,
    "Rank": 30,
    "question": "Which Iraqi city is the second largest in the Arab world after Cairo, Egypt?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Hanoi",
    "Wronganswer2": "Wuhan",
    "Wronganswer3": "Tehran",
    "CORRECT": "Baghdad",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0200",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 3,
    "Rank": 35,
    "question": "Which American President held the first Fourth of July celebration at the White House in 1801?",
    "Wronganswer1": "George Washington",
    "Wronganswer2": "John Adams",
    "Wronganswer3": "Abraham Lincoln",
    "CORRECT": "Thomas Jefferson",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0188",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 3,
    "Rank": 37,
    "question": "Which city in Mali has been a world center of Islamic learning from the 13th to the 17th century?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Sikasso",
    "Wronganswer2": "Mopti",
    "Wronganswer3": "Bamako",
    "CORRECT": "Timbuktu",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0186",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 3,
    "Rank": 56,
    "question": "In which region of Africa is the landlocked country Mali located?",
    "Wronganswer1": "South Africa",
    "Wronganswer2": "North Africa",
    "Wronganswer3": "East Africa",
    "CORRECT": "West Africa",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0194",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 3,
    "Rank": 57,
    "question": "The capital of Zimbabwe was officially called Salisbury until 1982. What is it called now?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Bulawayo",
    "Wronganswer2": "Mutare",
    "Wronganswer3": "Chitungwiza",
    "CORRECT": "Harare",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0213",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 3,
    "Rank": 58,
    "question": "In what place would you come across the Storbaelt bridge?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Italy",
    "Wronganswer2": "Spain",
    "Wronganswer3": "France",
    "CORRECT": "Denmark",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0217",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 3,
    "Rank": 79,
    "question": "According to Forbes 2013, which Russian city holds the largest number of billionaire residents in the world?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Mumbai",
    "Wronganswer2": "Dhaka",
    "Wronganswer3": "Guangzhou",
    "CORRECT": "Moscow",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0203",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 3,
    "Rank": 82,
    "question": "What does EPCOT refer to?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Experimental Postal Consortium Of Trinidad",
    "Wronganswer2": "Experimental People Cloning Operation Testing",
    "Wronganswer3": "Excalibur Producing Centers Of Tinseltown",
    "CORRECT": "Experimental Prototype Community Of Tomorrow",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0204",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 3,
    "Rank": 91,
    "question": "What vivid color do people in the Maasai tribe of Kenya always wear?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Black",
    "Wronganswer2": "Lavender",
    "Wronganswer3": "Green",
    "CORRECT": "Red",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0216",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 3,
    "Rank": 109,
    "question": "Which Egyptian city is called \"Umm al-Dunya\", meaning \"the mother of the world\"?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Dhaka",
    "Wronganswer2": "Lahore",
    "Wronganswer3": "Shenzhen",
    "CORRECT": "Cairo",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0211",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 3,
    "Rank": 110,
    "question": "Bolivia is covered by rainforest in what percentage?",
    "Wronganswer1": "0.85",
    "Wronganswer2": "0.05",
    "Wronganswer3": "0.18",
    "CORRECT": "0.4",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0206",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 3,
    "Rank": 127,
    "question": "Under what river is Queensway Tunnel set?",
    "Wronganswer1": "River Severn",
    "Wronganswer2": "River Tyne",
    "Wronganswer3": "River Dart",
    "CORRECT": "River Mersey",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0187",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 3,
    "Rank": 133,
    "question": "Which is the third longest river in Africa that runs through Mali?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Congo River",
    "Wronganswer2": "Yangzi River",
    "Wronganswer3": "Nile",
    "CORRECT": "Niger River",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0191",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 3,
    "Rank": 134,
    "question": "How many capital cities does South Africa have?",
    "Wronganswer1": "1",
    "Wronganswer2": "7",
    "Wronganswer3": "5",
    "CORRECT": "3",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0193",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 3,
    "Rank": 153,
    "question": "What is Zimbabwe's national emblem, appearing on the national flag and coat of arms of the country?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Zimbabwe Fish",
    "Wronganswer2": "Zimbabwe Antelope",
    "Wronganswer3": "Zimbabwe Dragon",
    "CORRECT": "Zimbabwe Bird",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0196",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 3,
    "Rank": 158,
    "question": "Russia and which other country border Estonia?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Lithuania",
    "Wronganswer2": "Finland",
    "Wronganswer3": "Belarus",
    "CORRECT": "Latvia",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0201",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 3,
    "Rank": 163,
    "question": "Tower Bridge is situated in which city?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Paris",
    "Wronganswer2": "Barcelona",
    "Wronganswer3": "Shanghai",
    "CORRECT": "London",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0190",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 3,
    "Rank": 167,
    "question": "How many official languages does South Africa have?",
    "Wronganswer1": "10",
    "Wronganswer2": "5",
    "Wronganswer3": "7",
    "CORRECT": "11",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0195",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 3,
    "Rank": 168,
    "question": "Which large species of eagle is the national bird of Zimbabwe and Zambia?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Bald Eagle",
    "Wronganswer2": "Harpy Eagle",
    "Wronganswer3": "Golden Eagle",
    "CORRECT": "African Fish Eagle",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0197",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 3,
    "Rank": 194,
    "question": "In Slovakia, what do you mean by saying \"dobre rano\" to somebody?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Good Night",
    "Wronganswer2": "Welcome",
    "Wronganswer3": "Good Bye",
    "CORRECT": "Good Morning",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0212",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 3,
    "Rank": 201,
    "question": "How many time zones does Brazil cover?",
    "Wronganswer1": "1 Time Zone",
    "Wronganswer2": "6 Time Zones",
    "Wronganswer3": "10 Time Zones",
    "CORRECT": "3 Time Zones",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0207",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 3,
    "Rank": 203,
    "question": "It is what river that flows from the Andes mountains onto the west and divides Chile's capital Santiago in two?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Amazon River",
    "Wronganswer2": "Nile",
    "Wronganswer3": "Yangtze River",
    "CORRECT": "Mapocho River",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0185",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 3,
    "Rank": 206,
    "question": "It is what traditional Malian drink that is served three times from the same pot?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Malian Tamarind",
    "Wronganswer2": "Guava Juice",
    "Wronganswer3": "Malian Coffee",
    "CORRECT": "Malian Tea",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0198",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 3,
    "Rank": 231,
    "question": "You would find \"Sento\", or neighborhood bathhouses in which country?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Thailand",
    "Wronganswer2": "Mexico",
    "Wronganswer3": "Brazil",
    "CORRECT": "Japan",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0202",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 3,
    "Rank": 238,
    "question": "Which country has the famous tourist attraction the Chapel Bridge?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Canada",
    "Wronganswer2": "Russia",
    "Wronganswer3": "Turkey",
    "CORRECT": "Switzerland",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0181",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 3,
    "Rank": 241,
    "question": "Into what ocean would the Gambia River empty after flow along the entire length of the Gambia?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Pacific Ocean",
    "Wronganswer2": "Indian Ocean",
    "Wronganswer3": "Arctic Ocean",
    "CORRECT": "Atlantic Ocean",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0189",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 3,
    "Rank": 244,
    "question": "What is the name of Morocco's capital, which translates to \"fortified place\"?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Fez",
    "Wronganswer2": "Marrakesh",
    "Wronganswer3": "Casablanca",
    "CORRECT": "Rabat",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0208",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 3,
    "Rank": 265,
    "question": "Which is closest size to Latvia in the four countries that border Latvia?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Estonia",
    "Wronganswer2": "Russia",
    "Wronganswer3": "Belarus",
    "CORRECT": "Lithuania",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0182",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 3,
    "Rank": 279,
    "question": "Which small country in West Africa is \"the Smiling Coast of Africa\" referred to?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Mali",
    "Wronganswer2": "Mauritania",
    "Wronganswer3": "Senegal",
    "CORRECT": "The Gambia",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0180",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 3,
    "Rank": 281,
    "question": "It is which country in West Africa that almost completely surrounds the Gambia?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Guinea",
    "Wronganswer2": "Mali",
    "Wronganswer3": "Mauritania",
    "CORRECT": "Senegal",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0205",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 3,
    "Rank": 290,
    "question": "What is the name of the hotel in Scotland which boasts a golf course designed by Jack Nicklaus?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Pitlochry",
    "Wronganswer2": "St. Andrews",
    "Wronganswer3": "Loch Lomond",
    "CORRECT": "Gleneagles",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0183",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 3,
    "Rank": 295,
    "question": "What is the name of the the smallest country on mainland Africa?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Zambia",
    "Wronganswer2": "Rwanda",
    "Wronganswer3": "Seychelles",
    "CORRECT": "The Gambia",
    "pic": 0
  },
  {
    "questionid": "TRA0210",
    "category": "Travel",
    "diff_rank": 3,
    "Rank": 303,
    "question": "What can you visit in the Grand Canyon on the Havasupai Indian Reservation?",
    "Wronganswer1": "Geyser",
    "Wronganswer2": "Glacier",
    "Wronganswer3": "Amusement Park",
    "CORRECT": "Waterfall",
    "pic": 0
  }
]
